allthewebsites.org 2018-02-18

# Privacy Policy : AllTheWebSites - Allthewebsites.org

Your privacy is **important** to us. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this site, **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG**

We have taken every effort to design our Web site to be useful, informative, helpful and honest. Please take a few minutes to look over the following Terms and Conditions because by using our site you automatically agree to them. Naturally, if you do not agree, please do not use the site. We reserve the right to make any modifications that we deem necessary at any time. Please continue to check these terms to see what those changes may be!

Your continued use of the this web site means that you accept these terms. THANK YOU FOR VISITING! 

This website uses Cookies, in some sections of the website, to personalize your browsing experience. These cookies are stored on your browser. Cookies are used enhance your use of the website. If your browser does not support cookies, or you have not enabled cookies on your browser, many of these timesaving features will not work properly. Cookies cannot store any virus codes on your computer. Also our site captures IP addresses and these will be used only for statistical purposes. 

Our site's forms ( registration form, contact form etc.,) requires you to input correct contact and demographic information.

This Website uses both outside advertising agencies and an inhouse adrotation program to display adverts (or Creatives) on the webpages. We have no control over Cookies set by outside advertising agencies. Members and visitors are hereby requested to consult the privacy statements of those external ad networks, whenever visiting the websites through links.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information may be collected and used by others. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. 

**Third Party Web sites and Links**

**WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** may reference, recommend, co-brand with or provide links to third party web sites. While **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** strives to select third party partners who have or share the same standards in regards to privacy policies comparable to its own, the user agrees that with respect to such web sites, **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** does not make any representation or warranty regarding the same, nor will **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** be responsible to the user or anyone else for any products, services or other material that may be sold, licensed, distributed or promoted on such web sites or in any manner for any content on such web sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Newsletter**

We will never sell or give out your e-mail address or any other personal information we get unless required by law. You can opt-out from getting newsletter by unsubscribing. Intructions for unsubscribing can be found in the Newsletter you receive. We will not spam and we are strictly against it.

**Contests and Sweepstakes**

Occasionally, **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** may run contests and sweepstakes and other promotions on its Web site or through its service, in which we request entrants to provide their name, address, e-mail address and other demographic details. In some cases, entrants may be required to answer survey questions. **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** uses the information collected in the entry form to verify the entrant's identity and to communicate with entrants. **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** will not share any of the entrant's personal or identifying information with any third party, unless required by law. **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** may make information about entrants available in aggregated form to advertisers, partners and the general public. 

**Surveys**

Occasionally, **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** may conduct a survey in order to target advertisements and content and to better understand a member's needs relating to the **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** Services. **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** will not share survey information about individuals with any third party. **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** may share, in aggregate form, information it collects from these surveys with its advertisers and partners. 

**Changes in Privacy Statement**

If **WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG** decides to change any of its privacy policies, the changes will be posted here. We reserve the right, at our discretion to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please make sure to check this page periodically for any changes. 

**Advertising Disclosures And Disclaimers**

This website is a collaborative site made and maintained by a group of individuals. Some part of the content (articles, webdirectory submissions) are user-generated-content (UGC) and the author of the content may or may not have a separate disclosure. This website accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions, affiliations or other forms of compensation to support this website ( hosting, maintenance etc.,). Information on this site is shared "as is". No warranties are made or implied. Website owners are held harmless from any actions by, or claims against, the companies represented herein. 

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this website. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this website may get compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this website receives compensation for the posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this website are purely the authors' own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question. 

This website does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content may not always be identified.

Part of the disclosures are made with help of http://www.disclosurepolicy.org

**Children**

WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us through the feedback form. 

WWW.ALLTHEWEBSITES.ORG reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes.

If you have any questions or concern, please contact us via feedback form on this website. 

Last Updated: 19 Dec 2009
